Preliminary Guide to the Kenneth W. Brooks Architectural Drawings 1963-circa 1999
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Folder 4
  - Fire Station Number One (remodel) Second Floor/Mezzanine HVAC [M-4], 1990 (Folder 4, Item 173)
  - Fire Station Number One (remodel) Details [M-5], 1990 (Folder 4, Item 174)
  - Fire Station Number One (remodel) Electrical Symbols List; General Notes; Demolition Notes; Fixture Schedule; Remodel Notes; Kitchen Notes, 1990 (Folder 4, Item 175)
  - Fire Station Number One (remodel) Partial Basement Plan; First Floor Plan [E-2], 1990 (Folder 4, Item 176)
  - Fire Station Number One (remodel) partial Basement Plan; First Floor Plan [E-3], 1990 (Folder 4, Item 177)
  - Fire Station Number One (remodel) Second Floor Power/Systems Plan; Partial Second Floor Lighting Plan; Mezzanine Lighting Plan [E-4], 1990 (Folder 4, Item 178)
  - Fire Station Number One (remodel) First Floor Systems Plan; Partial Basement Systems Plan [E-5], 1990 (Folder 4, Item 179)
  - Fire Station Number One (remodel) Alarm Panels A, B, C, D [E-6], 1990 (Folder 4, Item 180)
  - Fire Station Number One (remodel) Record Drawing: Supplemental Drawings [A-10] (Blank), 1990 (Folder 4, Item 181)
  - Fire Station Number Fifteen Addition and Remodel: Floor Plan/ Site Plan [A1], 1991 (Folder 4, Item 182)
  - Spokane Fire Department Fire Station Number Four: Addition and Remodel: Floor/Site Plan Design Development Phase, 1991 (Folder 4, Item 183)
  - Spokane Fire Department Stations Numbers Four and Fifteen Remodel, Spokane, Washington: Station Fifteen Floor Plan, Site Plan and Plan Details [A-6], 1991 (Folder 4, Item 184)
  - Spokane Fire Department Stations Numbers Four and Fifteen Remodel, Spokane, Washington: Station Number Four Floor Plan/Details [A-2], 1991 (Folder 4, Item 185)
- Folder 5
  - Stevens County Court House Remodel: Title Sheet and Index, 1984 (Folder 5, Item 186)
  - Stevens County Court House Remodel: Project Alternates Key Plans [A-1], 1984 (Folder 5, Item 187)
  - Stevens County Court House Remodel: Basement Floor Plan and Interior Elevations [A-2], 1984 (Folder 5, Item 188)
  - Stevens County Court House Remodel: Auditor's Office Floor Plan and Interior Elevations [A-3], 1984 (Folder 5, Item 189)
  - Stevens County Court House Remodel: Sheriff's Department Floor Plan and Interior Elevations [A-4], 1984 (Folder 5, Item 190)
  - Stevens County Court House Remodel: Public Works Department Floor Plan and Interior Elevations [A-5], 1984 (Folder 5, Item 191)
  - Stevens County Court House Remodel: Superior Court Floor Plan and Interior Elevations [A-6], 1984 (Folder 5, Item 192)
  - Stevens County Court House Remodel: Stair Plans, Details and Sections [A-7], 1984 (Folder 5, Item 193)
  - Stevens County Court House Remodel: Details [S-1], 1984 (Folder 5, Item 194)
  - Stevens County Court House Remodel: Partial First Floor Framing Plan, Structural Notes and Details [S-2], 1984 (Folder 5, Item 195)
  - Stevens County Court House Remodel: Schedules and Details [M-1], 1984 (Folder 5, Item 196)
  - Stevens County Court House Remodel: Basement Plumbing Plan [M-2], 1984 (Folder 5, Item 197)
  - Stevens County Court House Remodel: Basement HVAC Plan [M-3], 1984 (Folder 5, Item 198)
  - Stevens County Court House Remodel: Main Floor HVAC and Plumbing Plan [M-4], 1984 (Folder 5, Item 199)
  - Stevens County Court House Remodel: Lighting Fixture Schedule, Electrical Symbol and Remodel Notes [E-1], 1984 (Folder 5, Item 200)
  - Stevens County Court House Remodel: Basement Floor Plan- Power and Lighting [E-2], 1984 (Folder 5, Item 201)
  - Stevens County Court House Remodel: Auditor's Office Floor Plan- Power Lighting [E-3], 1984 (Folder 5, Item 202)
  - Stevens County Court House Remodel: Sheriff's Department Floor Plan- Power and Lighting [E-4], 1984 (Folder 5, Item 203)
  - Stevens County Court House Remodel: Public Work's Department Floor Plan- Power and Lighting [E-5], 1984 (Folder 5, Item 204)
  - Stevens County Court House Remodel: Superior Court Floor Plan- Power and Lighting [E-6], 1984 (Folder 5, Item 205)
  - United Church of Christ: Revised Interior Details:: Narthex East Elevation and Chancel West Elevation, 1964 (Folder 5, Item 206)
  - Community Congregational Church, Veradale, Washington: Foundation and Roof Framing Plans [A-1], 1963 (Folder 5, Item 207)
  - Community Congregational Church, Veradale, Washington: Revised Plans and Details at Nave. [A-4], 1964 (Folder 5, Item 208)
  - Community Congregational Church, Veradale, Washington: Floor Plan and Schedules [A-2], 1963 (Folder 5, Item 209)
  - Community Congregational Church, Veradale, Washington: Elevations and Exterior Details [A-3], 1963 (Folder 5, Item 210)
  - Community Congregational Church, Veradale, Washington: Mechanical Plans and Details [M-1], 1963 (Folder 5, Item 211)
  - Community Congregational Church, Veradale, Washington: Floor Plan, Schedules, Symbols and Risers [E-1], 1963 (Folder 5, Item 212)
  - Mount Carmel Hospital Addition and Remodel- Colville, Washington: Brooks, Hensley, Creager Office Set Three:: Bound Sheets [A-1]-[A-27] and [S-1]-[S-7], 1989 (Folder 5, Item 213)